To calculate the global pool to standard error, I'll first need to calculate
要计算全局总体标准误差
the number of users into the number of clicks in the control and
我首先需要计算对照组和实验组中的用户量和点击量
experiment groups globally by adding up the New Zealand data with the other data
将新西兰数据和其他数据全部加总起来
which gives these results.
得到这些结果
Then I can calculate the pooled probability and
然后我就可以计算总体概率和总体标准误差
the pooled standard error which come out to 0.051 and 0.0013.
它们分别是 0.051 和 0.0013
Recall that for New Zealand,
我记得新西兰的总体误差是 0.0042
the pooled error was 0.0042 which is about four times as large.
比这个值大四倍
In this case the variability of the global data
在这个例子中 根据总体标准误差
as measured by the pooled standard error is lower than the filtered data.
全局数据差异性较过滤数据低
Mostly because there is so much more data globally.
主要是因为全局数据要多很多
This will often be the case in practice.
在实际情况中也通常如此
But it's also good to keep in mind that, in practice,
但是请注意
your data will actually be a mix of different populations almost every time.
在实际工作中 数据几乎总是由不同的总体混合组成
When you filter, you're going to get a smaller but
通过筛选可以获得更小
also more uniform population.
更统一的总体
Which means that for the same number of data points,
这表示 对于相同数量的数据点
the variability of the filtered data is likely to be lower.
经筛选数据的差异性可能更低
In order to find whether the difference was statistically significant we first
为了查明其差异在统计学上是否具有重大影响
need to calculate the difference which globally was 0.0013.
我们首先需要计算出全局差异 就是 0.0013
Then I'll construct a confidence interval and see if it includes 0.
然后我要构建一个置信区间 看它是否包含 0
The margin of error will be the pooled standard error times the z score
误差范围等于总体标准误差乘以 z 分数 1.96
of 1.96 which comes to 0.0025.
结果是 0.0025
Since the margin of error is wider than the estimated difference,
由于误差范围大于估计的差异
the confidence interval will include 0.
置信区间将包含 0
Which means that this difference is not significant.
这表示这个差异不具有重大影响
Carrying out the same calculations for the New Zealand data,
对新西兰数据执行相同的计算
the difference observed is 0.012.
观察到的差异为 0.012
And the margin of error is 0.0082.
误差范围是 0.0082
In this case, the margin of error is smaller than the observed difference.
在这个例子中 误差范围小于观察到的差异
So the confidence interval will not include 0.
置信区间不包含 0
And the results are significant.
表示结果有重大影响
Note that even though the New Zealand only data had a higher variability, and
注意 虽然新西兰数据的差异性较高
thus a wider margin of error, or a wider confidence interval,
其误差范围较宽 也就是置信区间较宽
the New Zealand results were significant whereas the global results were not,
但是在全局结果没有重大影响时 新西兰结果却具有重大影响
because the observed difference was so
因为就新西兰数据观察到的差异要高得多
much higher in New Zealand, 0.012 versus 0.0013.
0.012 对比 0.0013
Adding all of the unaffected traffic that was outside of New Zealand
将所有新西兰以外的未受影响的点击量加总起来
diluted the difference in the global data,
稀释全局数据的差异
causing the result not to be significant.
使得其结果不具重大影响
To summarize, the global pooled standard error was 0.0013.
总结一下 全局总体标准误差为 0.0013
The New Zealand results were significant.
新西兰结果具有重大影响
And the global results were not.
全局结果不具有重大影响